cardkingdom.com 2018-06-30

# Card Kingdom - Magic: the Gathering, MTG, Magic Cards, Singles, EDH, Decks and Supplies

#### Card Kingdom Privacy Policy Overview

As a customer of Card Kingdom, we take the protection and proper use of your personal information seriously and are committed to protecting your personal information in our possession. In order to preserve your trust, we want you to understand what personal information we may collect from you, how we use such information and the choices you have regarding our use of this information.  

In this policy, "personal information" means any information by which you can be identified or contacted, such as your name (first and last), address (city, state, zip), email address, telephone number, etc.  

This Privacy Policy governs your experience on this website unless otherwise indicated.

#### What Information We Collect

We collect a variety of types of information. Examples include:

  * Contact information, such as your name, address, phone number, or email address; 
  * Purchase information, such as the items you purchase or sell to us, payment method and payment information (such as debit or credit card number and information), billing and shipping address, and contact information (such as for receipts or order updates); 
  * Preference information, such as your contact and marketing preferences 
  * Profile and account information, which may include Contact, Purchase, and Preference information as well as your account password, items in your online shopping cart or saved for future purchase, gift card or store credit balances, support ticket history, and other information about your profile or account; 
  * Demographic information, which may include birthdate if you provide it, ZIP code, and other information about you; 
  * Location information of your device that you use with our mobile application, if your device settings allow us to collect location information; and 
  * Device and browser information, including information about your phone, tablet, computer, or device, and online browsing activity (collectively, “automatically collected information”). Automatically collected information may include IP addresses, device and browser settings and information. Automatically collected information also may include information about when and how you access and use our website or mobile application, such as the date and time of your visit or use. 

#### How We Use Your Information

We use the personal information that we and our service providers collect to conduct our business and to provide you with the best possible experience. We may collect and use your information to provide you products, to respond to your comments, questions or complaints, determine your satisfaction with service, to personalize your experiences, and, if you've asked us to, send you marketing communications, and other information you have chosen to receive regarding our products, services, or special events.

We also use your personal information for our everyday business purposes such as service improvements, security, payment processing, analytics, operations, fraud detection and prevention, reporting, making back-ups and legal compliances.

#### How We Share Your Information

To best serve you, we may share your personal information with service providers that provide support services to us that help us administer our programs, operations, fulfill your requests, surveys, and contests. Service providers, third parties who perform services on our behalf, are contractually restricted from using your information in any manner other than in helping us to provide you with the products and services available from Card Kingdom. We may also, in certain instances, disclose your personal information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify you, contact you, detect and protect you or us from fraud or theft, manage information security or bring legal action to protect your rights or the rights of Card Kingdom or others. We may also disclose your personal information when you ask us to do so or when we believe it is required or permitted by law.

#### Links to Other Websites and Services

The Card Kingdom website and social media channels may include links to other Internet sites, content or videos (embedded or direct links) maintained by third parties ('Linked Sites'). Card Kingdom provides Linked Sites to you solely as a convenience, and the inclusion of Linked Sites does not imply endorsement by Card Kingdom of the Linked Sites. You access Linked Sites at your own risk, and by accessing them you leave Card Kingdom's website. Linked Sites are not under the control of Card Kingdom and Card Kingdom is not responsible for the contents of any Linked Site, including the privacy policies or tracking technologies they may use. We encourage you to check the applicable privacy policy to determine how they will handle any personally identifying information they collect from you.

#### Your Subscription, Your Choice

To update us with your preferences, you may unsubscribe via your Card Kingdom account profile.

#### Your Access

We respect your need to be able to access and update the personal information that you have provided to us. You may access and update your personal information at any time by logging into your account.

#### Children's Privacy

Card Kingdom will never knowingly request or collect personal information from any person under 16 years of age without prior verifiable parental consent. If you are under 16 years old, please do not provide your information on our website.

If we become aware that an individual is under the age of 16 and has submitted any information to Card Kingdom for any purpose without prior verifiable parental consent, we will delete his or her information from our files.

#### Security

To help guard your information, our checkout uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). SSL encrypts your credit card number, name and address so only Card Kingdom can decode your information. Please note that email is not encrypted and is not considered to be a secure means of transmitting credit card information.

#### Business Transitions

As we continue to develop our business, we may undergo a business transition such as acquiring another company, merging with an existing company or selling a portion of our assets. In such transitions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. In the unlikely event that Card Kingdom, Inc. or substantially all of its assets are acquired or enter a court proceeding, you acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that your personal information can continue to be used as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

#### Updates to This Policy

We may make changes to this Policy, and may apply any changes to information previously collected, as permitted by law. When we make material changes to this Policy, we will notify you by posting the updated Policy on our website, and we will update the effective date at the end of this Policy.

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:  

**Card Kingdom**  
5105 Leary Ave NW, Seattle, WA 98107 206-523-2273  
Or  
[Send](https://cardkingdom.freshdesk.com/support/tickets/new) us a support ticket. <https://cardkingdom.freshdesk.com/support/tickets/new>  

Effective Date 05/24/2018
